
export const questionsData = [
    {
        question: "JSON stands for _______.",
        id: 1,
        options: [
            "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "Java Object Notation",
            "JavaScript Object Normalization",
            "JavaScript Object-Oriented Notation"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "JSON is a _____ for storing and transporting data.",
        id: 2,
        options: [
            "xml format",
            "text format",
            "JavaScript",
            "php format"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "text format",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "The JSON syntax is a subset of the _____ syntax.",
        id: 3,
        options: [
            "Ajay",
            "Php",
            "Html",
            "Javascript"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Javascript",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the creator of JSON?",
        id: 4,
        options: [
            "Alvin Alexander",
            "Rasmus Lerdorf",
            "Douglas Crockford",
            "Jesse James Garrett"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Douglas Crockford",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "In the JSON syntax, data is separated by _____.",
        id: 5,
        options: [
            "Semicolons",
            "Colons",
            "Commas",
            "Hyper"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Commas",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "In the JSON syntax, array is written within in ____.",
        id: 6,
        options: [
            "Square brackets",
            "Curley braces",
            "Paratheses",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Square brackets",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "What are the features of JSON?",
        id: 7,
        options: [
            "Simplicity",
            "Openness",
            "Self-Describing",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the correct symbol to insert a comment in JSON?",
        id: 8,
        options: [
            "//",
            "/*…*/",
            "<!-- … -->",
            "JSON doesn't support the comments"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "JSON doesn't support the comments",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "In the JSON syntax, data is in ____ pairs.",
        id: 9,
        options: [
            "class/object",
            "name/value",
            "datatype/variable",
            "value/="
        ],
        correctAnswer: "name/value",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },
    {
        question: "JSON names (keys) require double quotes?",
        id: 10,
        options: [
            "True",
            "False",
            "None of the Above",
            "All of the Above"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "True",
        choosedAnswer: null
    },

]
